viracure.com 2015-09-09

# Privacy Policy | Viracure

We, Viracure Limited, take your privacy very seriously. This privacy policy governs and details the main privacy principles we apply regarding information and data collected through the services provided through our website: www.viracure.com (the “Website”). 

BY VISITING OUR WEBSITE, YOU AGREE WITH THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT.

In the Website, the antivirus product is offered by our affiliate, Woggle Trading Limited (the “Woggle Product”). If you purchase a license to the Woggle Product, please read carefully the end user license that includes additional and other terms regarding the collection and use of information and data. 

In order to use programs that are available for download in this Website (the “Programs”), you may be requested to fill in a detailed form. During such registration, you will be requested to submit information such as; full name, post address, email address, detailed payment method information.

When purchasing license to the Programs, we ask for your full contact details along with your billing and personal address information. This information will be used for processing the order, receiving the payment information required and to enable you to use services and programs you have selected and purchased a license for. Should there be a problem with any order, one of our representatives may contact you via email or phone in order to clarify. Remember that the confirmation email of each purchase and transaction is sent to the exact address you gave us, so make sure it is correct.

If you are under 18 years old, please avoid using this website do not download any of the Programs and do not use any of the Programs.

While downloading the Programs, you may be requested for your contact information and email address. You may get email messages from us that relate to any transaction. The email subjects may include download referral links, activation software information, help & support alerts, and upgrades for the software full version with updates included.

We may collect some information relating to you that may include among others your IP Address, browser type, operating system version, GUID identification, customer configuration, the hardware identification number of the computer or other machine used, whether you are Administrator, or not, version of the operating system and service pack and whether your windows operating system is 32 or 64 bit, some internal tracking identifiers that we use to track downloads, installs, sales, and uninstalls and your using behavior of the Programs.

Such information collected is used to carry out the services provided by the Programs, as well as for newsletter subscriptions, personalization of the user experience on the software, marketing and promotional purposes, including remarketing, research and improvement of the Programs, to notify you of new services or changes to existing services, to send you technical or service-related communications and to enforce the Terms of use of the Website and Programs.

While downloading the programs it may also include third party software that collects browsing non-identifiable information and behavioral preferences, by adding tracking technologies such as cookies that track the types of content you have viewed and suggest you accordingly advertisements that might be relevant for you.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies and similar technologies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Web beacons may also be disabled by disabling JavaScript on your computer. However, alteration of such settings may affect the functionality of our Website. For more information on how to disable cookies, you may visit www.aboutcookies.org. We understand that you may wish to stop sharing with us any of your information. In order to stop sharing with us your information, please uninstall our program and do not use the Website. Information collected prior to such uninstall will be still kept with us and may be used by us, as used prior to such uninstall.

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy our assets and rights. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets in such transaction. We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our End User License and or Terms of Use or protect our others rights. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

You have a right to access the personal data that is held about you. To obtain a copy of your personal information, please send an email to [support@viracure.com](mailto:support@viracure.com): (in the title, copy and paste this: “Obtain a copy of my personal information”) or submit such application at: <https://www.viracure.com/en/homepage-responsive/#nav_section_support>.

Our Website and our newsletter may include various links to third party websites or promote third party products. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third parties in any way. We strongly suggest that you refer to their privacy policy before accessing any website or making any purchase from them. 

Please note that this policy may change from time to time. All updates will be published at this Website. We encourage you to refer to this policy periodically.

This Privacy Policy will be governed by the laws of Cyprus. The exclusive jurisdiction and venue to adjudicate any dispute arising out of this Privacy Policy shall be of the courts of Cyprus excluding conflict of laws. 

Any claim or other legal notice must be sent to our address: Viracure Limited  
89 Bond Street,  
London, UK W1S 1DA.

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy or if you believe that this website is not following its stated privacy policy, or if you wish to update the information you provided us please send an email to: [support@viracure.com](mailto:support@viracure.com).
